Hi everyone and welcome to this new video. I'm going to introduce you to one of my all-time
favorite everyday wear brands. If you don't like cats you can skip this video but leave a thumbs
up anyway. No, just kidding. I love cats so I love Gothic Cat. I encountered Gothic Cat some years
ago at the Wave Gothic Treffen in Leipzig and they do make funny t-shirts and pillows and blankets
and whatever with cat motives yay and goth cat motives so gothic cat yeah so
their basics are of course t-shirts for men and women but they also have tank
tops and other stuff and few leggings and maybe you know the Joy Division art
but this is not a Joy Division it's the Meow Division leggings and I think it's
one of the most famous motives but as I said it's not only for people who like
gothic but also for people who like puns for example because I think they're
hilarious and people who like cats alright so this basically was it I
wanted to show you what I'm wearing if I'm not wearing all the stuff in the
videos because let's be honest in my daily life I'm not wearing cat seats all
the time haha cat suits and I'm not wearing all the PVC stuff but this kind of stuff because I
think it's fun and it's black and it has cats and I like it and I hope you like it too have a look
in the description text I'll link the shop down below if you buy something via this link I earn
a small commission and you can help supporting this channel because I'll upload another video
soon and I hope you're going to stick around and have fun with this one bye
Thank you.